midasplayer.com 2011-04-27

# Datenschutzerklärung - Kundendienst bei King.com - Kostenlose Spiele spielen

## PRIVACY STATEMENT

Welcome to the King.com website run by Midasplayer.com Limited ("we," "us," and "our"). We are committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of our King.com website (the "Site") (we refer to the Site and the services we provide as described in our Site collectively as the "Site Features"). As such, we have established and implemented this privacy statement to inform visitors to the Site and users of the Site Features how we use and protect the information we collect. If you have any questions regarding this information or our privacy practices, please see the section entitled "Questions? Contact Us" at the end of this privacy statement. This privacy statement was last updated on June 24, 2009. 

### What information does King.com collect?

We do not collect personally identifiable information unless our Members voluntarily provide it to us. We do, however, collect certain types of information and ask for personal information in certain circumstances, such as when you set up an account. The following sections describe what type of information we collect, when we collect it and how we use it. 

### Setting up an account

In order to use certain functionality of the Site Features, you will have to create a user account which requires you to submit certain personal information. When you register and create an account, we require you to provide us with a user name of your choosing, your email address, your country of residence and a unique password. When you upgrade your account to Gold status, we require your name, billing address and credit, debit or charge card or PayPal account information. In addition, as a Gold member, you can include information you determine in your “player profile” and may upload photographs to your Player profile. 

### Cookies

Cookies are small bits of electronic information that a web site can transfer to a visitor’s hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many web sites use them. Cookies allow web site operators to better customize visits to the site to the visitor’s individual preferences. For example, by setting a cookie you would not have to enter information in the Site more than once, thereby saving time. We do not receive or record any personal information in the cookies we use. We do use cookies to enable our system to recognize your computer, and to ensure that your account is attributed to the user who inputs the correct username and password for that account. We may also use cookies to serve advertising banners for our Game Service to you. These banners may be served by us or by a third party on our behalf. Again, these cookies will not contain any personal information. 

Although most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your browser to prevent that or to notify you when you are sent a cookie. Even without accepting a cookie, you can still access the Site Features. 

### Use of Email Notifications

We utilize e-mails to notify you when you win tournaments, alert you to withdrawals and to let you know of special promotions, events and policy changes. Important notices will be sent to your nominated email address as long as your account is open, but you have the choice to opt-in or opt-out of receiving any promotional e-mails at any time by sending an email to that effect, using the dedicated form. We do not transfer or share your email address with any third parties. 

### How do we use the information you provide us?

As stated above, we use your personal information such as your name, address, billing and mailing address and credit card number for billing purposes when we charge you for the use of your account. We also will use your email address to contact you as described above. 

By registering as a Member, you agree that we may display the username you select, tournament scores and records. By accepting any prize, you further agree that in our promotional efforts we have the right to publish your username and tournament records in any media (newsletters, broadcasts, emails, etc.), without making any payment to you. 

We reserve the right to collect general demographic and other anonymous information that does not personally identify you. This information is not associated with your personally identifiable information and cannot be linked to you personally. We may also provide aggregated information about our visitors to outside parties from time to time. 

We may also disclose your personal information to one of our partners if you registered with us as a Member after clicking on a link on their website and you agreed that we could disclose such information to them. 

In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of our assets, Members’ information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Members will be notified via prominent notice on the Site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of information of users held by us. If as a result of the business transition, information will be used for a purpose different from that stated, or implied, at the time of collection users will be given a choice consistent with our notification of changes section. 

Notwithstanding any other term of this privacy statement, we may release any personal information we obtain or collect when we believe its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. 

## How does King.com protect Member information?

We implement a variety of security measures to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems. User personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems. Any credit card information you supply us is transmitted and protected via Secure Socket Layer technology ("SSL") and HTTPS protocol and then stored into our databases to be accessed only as stated above. 

It is important to us that everyone playing our games plays fairly and we treat any abuse very seriously. We therefore take a number of measures intended to prevent abuse and ensure the smooth and uninterrupted performance of our games. You therefore agree that we can monitor your computer closely to detect any kind of attempt to cheat and that we can also make use of "Active X" controls and other methods to ensure that our Games are played fairly. 

We will retain your personal data only as long as is necessary for the purposes to which you consent under this Member Agreement, and then we will delete it from our systems. 

## How do you opt in?

When you initially establish your account, you will be asked if you would like to opt in to receiving email notifications and updates. You can change this preference at any time by accessing the "My Account" area of the Site. 

### Notification of changes.

By visiting the Site or using the Site Features, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as set forth in this privacy statement. If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes within this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

### Questions? Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our use of your personal data, or you wish to change or update personal data you have previously provided to us, you can contact us using the dedicated form. You can also use this form if you wish to request from us a copy of the personal data we hold about you or a description of that data. Please note that by English law we are entitled to charge you a small sum for providing this information. 

### Terms and Conditions

Please also read the Terms of Use establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the Site and the Site Features.
